Guide to the Cornell University Board of Trustees records, 1865-2001.
Cornell University Board of Trustees records
- Series II. Executive Committee
  - Subseries Ia. Working Files
    - Working file, 1967-06 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Includes Report of the Fire Protection Committee, report of the University Commission on Residential Environment
    - Working file, 1967-07-1967-12 (Box 59, Folder 2-5)
    - Working file, 1967-07-1967-12 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Working file, 1968-01-1968-03 (Box 59, Folder 7-8)
    - Working file, 1968-01-1968-03 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Working file, 1968-04 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Working file, 1968-05-1968-07 (Box 60, Folder 1-3)
    - Working file, 1968-08-1968-09 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Working file, 1968-10-1968-12 (Box 60, Folder 5-7)
    - Working file, 1969-01-1969-03 (Box 60, Folder 8-19)
    - Working file, 1969-04 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Working file, 1969-05 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1969-06 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Working file, 1969-07 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Working file, 1969-08 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Working file, 1969-08 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Working file, 1969-09 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Working file, 1969-09 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1969-10 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Working file, 1969-11 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Working file, 1969-12 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Working file, 1970-01-1970-03 (Box 61, Folder 11-12)
    - Working file, 1970-04 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Working file, 1970-05 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1970-06-1970-12 (Box 62, Folder 2-7)
    - Working file, 1971-01-1971-04 (Box 62, Folder 8-11)
    - Working file, 1971-05-1971-12 (Box 63, Folder 1-7)
    - Working file, 1972-01 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Working file, 1972-02-1972-04 (Box 63, Folder 9-11)
    - Working file, 1972-05-1972-12 (Box 64, Folder 1-7)
    - Working file, 1973-01 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Working file, 1973-02 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Working file, 1973-03 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Working file, 1973-04-1973-12 (Box 65, Folder 1-8)
    - Working file, 1974-01 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Working file, 1974-02 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Working file, 1974-03-1974-04 (Box 65, Folder 11-12)
    - Working file, 1974-05-1974-12 (Box 66, Folder 1-7)
    - Working file, 1975-01-1975-05 (Box 66, Folder 8-12)
    - Working file, 1975-05-1975-12 (Box 67, Folder 1-6)
    - Working file, 1976-01-1976-05 (Box 67, Folder 7-10)
    - Working file, 1976-05 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1976-06-1976-12 (Box 68, Folder 2-7)
    - Working file, 1977-01-1977-05 (Box 68, Folder 8-11)
    - Working file, 1977-05-1977-12 (Box 69, Folder 1-6)
    - Working file, 1978-01 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1978-02-1978-03 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Working file, 1978-04 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Working file, 1978-05 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Working file, 1978-05 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Working file, 1978-06-1978-12 (Box 70, Folder 1-5)
    - Working file, 1979-01-1979-12 (Box 70, Folder 6-14)
    - Working file, 1980-01-1980-12 (Box 71, Folder 1-10)
    - Working file, 1981-01 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Working file, 1981-02-1981-03 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Working file, 1981-04-1981-09 (Box 71, Folder 13-16)
    - Working file, 1981-10-1981-12 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
    - Working file, 1982-01-1982-05 (Box 72, Folder 3-6)
    - Working file, 1982-07 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1982-08-1982-12 (Box 72, Folder 8-9)
    - Working file, 1983-01-1983-05 (Box 72, Folder 10-13)
    - Working file, 1983-07 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Working file, 1983-09-1983-12 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
    - Working file, 1984-01-1984-05 (Box 73, Folder 3-6)
    - Working file, 1984-07 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1984-07-1984-12 (Box 73, Folder 8-12)
    - Working file, 1985-01-1985-04 (Box 73, Folder 13-16)
    - Working file, 1985-05 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Working file, 1985-06 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Working file, 1985-07 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - Working file, 1985-08-1985-09 (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Working file, 1985-10-1985-12 (Box 74, Folder 31-33)
    - Working file, 1986-01 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Working file, 1986-03 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Working file, 1986-04-1986-05 (Box 74, Folder 36-37)
    - Working file, 1986-06 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1986-07-1986-12 (Box 75, Folder 2-5)
    - Working file, 1987-01-1987-04 (Box 75, Folder 6-9)
    - Working file, 1987-04 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Working file, 1987-05-1987-06 (Box 75, Folder 11-12)
    - Working file, 1987-09 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Working file, 1987-09-1987-12 (Box 75, Folder 14-16)
    - Working file, 1988-01 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Working file, 1988-02 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Working file, 1988-03-1988-05 (Box 75, Folder 19-21)
    - Working file, 1988-06 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Working file, 1988-09-1988-12 (Box 76, Folder 1-5)
    - Working file: joint meeting with the Development Steering Committee, 1988-12 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Working file, 1989-01-1989-08 (Box 76, Folder 7-13)
    - Working file, 1989-09-1989-10 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Working file, 1989-10-1989-12 (Box 76, Folder 15-17)
    - Appointment letters, 1985-07-1985-12 (Box 74, Folder 1-3)
    - Appointment letters, 1986-01-1986-09 (Box 74, Folder 4-7)
    - Appointment letters, 1986-10 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Appointment letters, 1986-11-1986-12 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Appointment letters, 1987-01-1987-12 (Box 74, Folder 10-15)
    - Appointment letters, 1988-05-1988-12 (Box 74, Folder 16-20)
    - Appointment letters, 1989-06-1989-09 (Box 74, Folder 21-22)
    - Working file, 1990-06-1990-12 (Box 74, Folder 23-27)
    - Working file, 1991-06 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Working file, 1994-01-1994-09 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Working file, 1994-10-1994-12 (Box 77, Folder 1-2)
    - Working file, 1995-01-1995-11 (Box 77, Folder 3-9)
    - Working file, 1995-12 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Working file, 1996-01-1996-12 (Box 77, Folder 11-19)
    - Working file, 1997-01-1997-12 (Box 77, Folder 20-24)
    - Working file, 1998-01-1998-08 (Box 77, Folder 25-28)
    - Working file, 1998-09-1998-12 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
    - Working file, 1999-04-1999-12 (Box 78, Folder 3-7)
    - Working file, 2000-01-2000-12 (Box 78, Folder 8-15)
    - Working file, 2001-01-2001-06 (Box 78, Folder 16-19)
  - Subseries IIb. Minutes
    There are no minutes present for years 1915-1938
    - Minutes, bound, 1868-1886 (Box 101)
    - Minutes, 1886-1896 (Box 100, Folder 1-3)
    - Minutes, 1897-1907 (Box 100, Folder 4-9)
    - Minutes, 1908-1914 (Box 100, Folder 10-14)
    - Minutes, 1939 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 1940 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Minutes, 1941 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Minutes, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Minutes, 1944-1945 (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Minutes, 1950- (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Minutes, 1955- (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Minutes, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Minutes, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Minutes, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - Minutes, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - Minutes, 1968-1972 (Box 79, Folder 1-5)
    - Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 79, Folder 6-10)
    - Minutes, 1978-1983 (Box 79, Folder 11-16)
    - Minutes, 1985-1990 (Box 79, Folder 17-22)
    - Minutes, 1994-2001 (Box 79, Folder 23-30)
- Series III. General Administration Committee
  - Subseries IIIa. Working Files
    Files includes correspondence, appointments, conspectus, resignations, resolutions, and budget documents
    - Working File, 1915-05 - 1915-12 (Box 52, Folder 1-4)
    - Working File, 1916-01 - 1916-12 (Box 52, Folder 5-9)
    - Working File, 1917-01 - 1917-04 (Box 52, Folder 10-12)
    - Working File, 1917-05 - 1917-06 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Includes correspondence regarding death of Professor Mauxion
    - Working File, 1917-07 - 1917-09 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Working File, 1917-10 - 1917-11 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      Includes copy of letter from Theodore Stanton gifting library to Sage College, copy of ground plan of the Bronz International Exposition
    - Working File, 1917-11 - 1917-12 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Working File, 1918-01 - 1918-03 (Box 52, Folder 17-18)
    - Working File, 1920-06 - 1920-10 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Includes report of housing conditions
    - Working File, 1920-12 - 1921-01 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Includes minutes of the Council of the Graduate School, statement concerning the training of teachers in the college of Arts and Sciences, second memorandum on Law professors' salaries
    - Working File, 1921-01 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Working File, 1921-02 - 1921-04 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Includes mid-year report of the department of Hygiene and Preventive Medicine, copy of Proposed Constitution of the Cornell Honor System
    - Working File, 1921-05 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Includes Law College faculty meeting minutes
    - Working File, 1921-06 - 1921-11 (Box 7, Folder 6-8)
    - Working File, 1922-01 - 1922-02 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Includes report of housing conditions, report on proposed Law School summer session
    - Working File, 1922-03 - 1922-04 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Includes letter in regard to the removal of sediment from Beebe Lake
    - Working File, 1922-05 - 1922-06 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Includes information on free tuition for children of faculty members
    - Working File, 1922-07 - 1922-12 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Working File, 1923-01 - 1923-05 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Includes information on the McMullen Settlement
    - Working File, 1923-06 - 1923-12 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Includes court ruling on Benno Loewy case
    - Working File, 1924-01 - 1924-05 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Working File, 1924-06 - 1924-12 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Working File, 1925-01 - 1925-05 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Working File, 1925-06 - 1925-09 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Includes letter to Farrand from faculty complaining about parking on campus,
    - Working File, 1925-10 - 1925-11 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
    - Working File, 1925-11 - 1926-01 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Working File, 1926-02 - 1926-12 (Box 7, Folder 8-10)
    - Working File, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 11-13)
    - Working File, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
    - Working File, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 17-19)
    - Working File, 1930-02 - 1930-06 (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
    - Working File, 1930-07 - 1930-09 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      Includes Forest Home Water Supply report
    - Working File, 1930-10 - 1930-12 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Working File, 1931-02 - 1931-03 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      Includes proposed scholarship fund of Cornell women
    - Working File, 1931-04 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Includes synopsis of will of John Henry Comstock
    - Working File, 1931-05 - 1931-10 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
    - Working File, 1931-12 - 1932-03 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Working File, 1932-03 - 1932-06 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Includes list of lost coats and clothing reported on campus
    - Working File, 1932-11 - 1932-12 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Working File, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
    - Working File, 1934-01 - 1934-09 (Box 8, Folder 9-11)
    - Working File, 1934-09 - 1934-12 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Includes proposed sketches of Sage Chapel choir changes
    - Working File, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 13-16)
    - Working File, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 17-20)
    - Working File, 1937-01 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Includes will of Robert Treman, letter regarding the motorizing of a battery of field artillery
    - Working File, 1937-02 - 1937-12 (Box 9, Folder 2-7)
    - Working File, 1938-01 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Includes report of the Committee on Student Aid
    - Working File, 1938-02 - 1938-12 (Box 9, Folder 9-12)
    - Working File, 1939-01 - 1939-05 (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
    - Working File, 1939-06 - 1939-09 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Includes reports on aeronautical engineering and television engineering
    - Working File, 1939-09 - 1939-10 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Working File, 1939-10 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Reports on Morrill-Nelson Land Grant, Department of Interior, 1913-1919 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Reports on Morrill-Nelson Land Grant, Department of Interior, 1920-1921 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Reports on Morrill-Nelson Land Grant, Department of Interior, 1922-1924 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Reports on Morrill-Nelson Land Grant, Department of Interior, 1924-1926 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Reports on Morrill-Nelson Land Grant, Department of Interior, 1927-1929 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Subseries IIIb. Minutes
    - Minutes, 1915-1920 (Box 97, Folder 7-10)
    - Minutes, 1921-1925 (Box 97, Folder 11-14)
    - Minutes, 1926-1930 (Box 97, Folder 15-20)
    - Minutes, 1931-1935 (Box 97, Folder 21-24)
    - Minutes, 1936-1939 (Box 97, Folder 25-28)
- Series IV. Council on the College of Veterinary Medicine
  - Subseries IVa. Working Files
    - Working file, 1913 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Working file, 1917 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Working file, 1920 - 1921 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Working file, 1922 - 1925 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Subseries IVb. Minutes
    - Minutes, 1910 - 1913 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Minutes, 1914 - 1915 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Minutes, 1916 - 1917 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Minutes, 1920 - 1921 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Minutes, 1922 - 1923 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Minutes, 1924 - 1925 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Minutes, 1940 - 1941 (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Series V. Medical College Council
  - Subseries Va. Working Files
    Includes budgets, reports, correspondence
    - Working files, 1921 - 1924 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Working files, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Working files, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Working files, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Working files, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Working files, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Working files, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Subseries Vb. Minutes
    - Minutes, 1898 - 1900 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1901 - 1904 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1905 - 1909 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1910 - 1914 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1915 - 1919 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1920 - 1921 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1922 - 1924 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1925 - 1929 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1930 - 1932 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1933 - 1936 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1937 - 1940 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Series VI. Agricultural College Council and State College Council
  The State College Council was charged with governing the New York State Colleges, including the New York State College of Agriculture, New York State College of Home Economics, New York State Veterinary College, and New York State Agricultural Experiment Station. The Council consisted of several Cornell University trustees, the deans or directors of three of the colleges in question, two (or sometimes three) faculty representatives, and the University Comptroller.
  - Subseries VIa. Agricultural College Council
    - Working files, / 1865 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1912 - 1913 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1914 - 1915 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Working file, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Includes a report of reasons why the College of Agriculture needs reorganization and redirection
    - 1916 - 1917 (Box 55, Folder 32)
      Includes copies of minutes
    - Working file, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Working file, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Working file, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Working file, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Working file, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1912 - 1925 (Box 14, Folder 10-17)
  - Subseries VIb. State College Council
    - Working files, / 1865 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1911 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Working file, 1925 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Working file, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 20-21)
    - Working file, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Working file, 1928 (Box 14, Folder 23-24)
    - Working file, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Working file, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
    - Working file, 1931-01 - 1931-05 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
    - Working file, 1931-06 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Includes map of distance of neighbors from Waite Barns
    - Working file, 1931-10 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Working file, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
    - Working file, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 11-13)
    - Working file, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
    - Working file, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
    - Working file, 1936-01 - 1936-05 (Box 15, Folder 18-20)
    - Working file, 1936-10 - 1936-11 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 2-4)
    - Working file, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
    - Working file, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
    - Minutes, 1925 - 1939 (Box 16, Folder 9-22)
    - State College Council Proceedings binder volume 1 and volume 2, 1930-1935 (Box 102)
      Printed meeting minutes bound in two small notebooks, with a typewritten name and subject index at the beginning of volume 1 and manuscript notes fastened in. Pages are numbered by hand. Topics covered in the minutes include the state colleges' finances, personnel changes (including appointments of county agricultural agents), and other administrative matters. Pages 316-318 at the end of volume 2 describe the discussion of the collection which became the Bailey Hortorium, the gift of Liberty Hyde Bailey.
    - Bound Proceedings of State College Council, 1927-1933 (Box 102)
    - Bound Proceedings of State College Council, 1933-1941 (Box 102)
    - Bound Proceedings of State College Council, 1941-1944 (Box 102)
- Series VII. Committee on Buildings and Grounds
  Files include contracts, correspondence, reports, conspectus, land sale and purchase information, and maps
  Includes Arboretum Committee, Architectural Advisory Board
  - Subseries VIIa. Working Files
    - Working file, 1914 - 1915 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Includes survey of Ithaca Plot R
    - Working file, 1916 - 1917 (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
      Includes request from women for pageant space, drill hall plans, and two photographs of bushes
    - Working file, 1920 - 1921-07 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Working file, 1921-08 - 1921-11 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Working file, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Includes plans of proposed changes in bathrooms in Risley Hall
    - Working file, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Working file, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      Includes report of the Plan Commission
    - Working file, 1925 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      Includes plan for proposed athletic fields, report of fire prevention
    - Working file, 1926 - 1927 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Working file, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Working file, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Working file, 1930 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Working file, 1931 (Box 56, Folder 14-15)
      Includes plans for proposed roads, Rockefeller Hall site, Ithaca Country Club plan, and other plans
    - Working file, 1932 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Working file, 1933 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Working file, 1934 (Box 56, Folder 18-19)
      Includes plan of garage at East Ave, curbing and road at Drill Hall, addition to swimming pool, 8" water main, retaining wall South Ave
    - Working file, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      Includes graphs of steam, electric, and water production
    - Working file, 1936 - 1937 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Working file, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 22-25)
    - Working file, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 26-29)
    - Working file, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 30-34)
      Includes rules and regulations for control of traffic and parking on campus
    - Working file, 1941 (Box 56, Folder 35)
      Includes catalogue of Fire Alarm boxes
    - Working file, 1941 (Box 56, Folder 36)
      Includes letter regarding the use of horses during wartime
    - Working file, 1941-03 - 1941-04 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Working file, 1942 (Box 56, Folder 38-41)
    - Working file, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Working file, 1944 (Box 56, Folder 43-44)
    - Working file, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Working file, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Working file, 1948 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Landscape Committee Working file and minutes, 1929 - 1935 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Subseries VIIb. Minutes
    - Minutes, 1914 - 1917 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1920 - 1921 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1922 - 1923 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1924 - 1925 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, 1930 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1932 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Minutes, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Minutes, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Minutes, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Minutes, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Minutes, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Minutes, 1943 - 1944 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Minutes, 1946 - 1948 (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Series VIII. Finance and Budget Committees
  - Subseries VIIIa. Finance Committee
    - Working File, 1915-03 - 1915-10 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    - Working File, 1916 (Box 53, Folder 3-5)
    - Working File, 1917 (Box 53, Folder 6-9)
    - Working File, 1920 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Working File, 1921 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Working File, 1922 (Box 53, Folder 12-13)
    - Working File, 1923 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Working File, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Working File, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Working File, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Working File, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Working File, 1928 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Working File, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Working File, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Working File, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Working File, 1932 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
    - Working File, 1933 (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
    - Working File, 1934 (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
    - Working File, 1935 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Working File, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1914 - 1917 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1920 - 1921 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1922 - 1923 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 1924 - 1925 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 1926 - 1928 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, 1929 - 1931 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Minutes, 1932 - 1933 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Minutes, 1934 - 1936 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Minutes, 1937 - 1939 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 1940 - 1943 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Subseries VIIIb. Budget Committee
    - Working File, 1927 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Working File, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Working File, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Working File, 1931 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Working File, 1932 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Working File, 1933 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Working File, 1935 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Working File, 1937 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Working File, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Working File, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 18-19)
    - Working File, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 1927 - 1934 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Minutes, 1935 - 1942 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Series IX. Minor Committees
  - Graduate School Council, 1922-02 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Fraternity Dormitory Committee, 1932-04 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Architectural Adviser Committee, 1930-05 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Engineering College Council, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Arboretum Policy Committee, 1942-03 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Student Houses, 1938 - 1940 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Joint Administration Board: New York State Hospital- Cornell Medical College, 1939-11-13 (Box 57, Folder 34)